Guide to the National Education Association-Film, Audio, and Video records, 1938-2011 NEA1010.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
National Education Association Film, Audio, and Video Collection
1938-2011, bulk 1952-2011
1952-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
National Education Association of the United States
NEA1010.RG
450.5 Linear Feet
Scope and Contents
Collections contains the moving image and audio recordings produced or held by the National Education Association. The collection contains three series reflecting the recording's purpose. The three series are:
Conventions; Educational Material; and Promotional Material.
Arrangement note
Collection: Organized into 3 series: Conventions; Educational Material; and Promotional Material.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Technical Requirements Note
Please be aware that Special Collections may not have the equipment to play all formats in this collection.
Labor unions; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Teachers; Education -- United States -- History
- Conventions, 1955-2001; Series 1; 85 Linear Feet
  Arrangement note
  Series is arranged alphanumerically by title, then chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  Series contains audio and moving image recordings from various conventions, conferences and workshops. Most of these recordings are from NEA conventions, the Annual Meeting/Representative Assembly prominent among them. The recordings include speakers, individual sessions, workshops, interviews and highlights.
  Technical Requirements Note
  Please be aware that Special Collections may not have the equipment to play all formats included in the collection.
  - 1. Interview with President Keith Geiger 2. Remarks to NEA-PAC Council, December 12, 1991; Series 1; BETACAM videotape (Box 4100, Folder 1)
  - 0010 NEA News Conference Alonso Tape 2, March 2, 1968; Series 1 (Box 3543, Folder 1)
    Alonso, Braulio
  - 0010 NEA News Conference - Tape 1 - (2 Million Dollars) Speaker Braulio Alonso, March 2, 1968; Series 1; 7 1/2 IPS Grant to 71a (Box 3543, Folder 2)
  - 0012 Taylor, Harold - Alonso News Conference 2, March 2, 1968; Series 1; Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company St. Paul 6, Mins (Box 3543, Folder 3)
  - 0035 Lambert, Sam Conference with AD & UPI - Alonso - 2:45, March 5, 1968; Series 1; 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3543, Folder 4)
    Lambert, Sam M.; Alonso, Braulio
  - 0036 Lambert, Sam News Conference - 11 AM The NEA Allen Rm. - Braulion Alonso, J. Lanly, Annoine of its 1968 Legislative Objective, January 9, 1968; Series 1 (Box 3543, Folder 5)
    Lambert, Sam M.
  - 0046 Ruth Stout and Carl Megel Annual Teacher - Board Banquet, December 10, 1962; Series 1; Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company St. Paul 6, Minn. (Box 3543, Folder 6)
    American Federation of Teachers. AFT; Stout, Ruth Albertine
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Arno Jewett - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas - Tails out, March 26, 1963; Series 1; 1.85 (Box 3543, Folder 7)
  - 1957 Centennial Hi-Lites - Philadelphia, Series 1; Magnetic audio tape soundtrack to a slide presentation. Slides were not present upon receipt at archives. (Box 3686, Folder 1)
  - 1979 Annual Meeting - John Ryor - Cassette Master, Series 1; Ryor, John; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS, 34:22 min. (Box 3698, Folder 6)
  - 1979 Annual Meeting - Ryor - Cassette Master Looped - Slave, Series 1; Ryor, John; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3717, Folder 1)
  - 1979 Annual Meeting - Terry Herndon - Cassette Master, Series 1; Herndon, Terry; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS, 30:28 min. (Box 3698, Folder 7)
  - 1994 RA Highlights, July 21, 1994; Series 1; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4028, Folder 1)
  - 1994 Teacher of the Year at NEA R.A., July 21, 1994; Series 1; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4028, Folder 2)
  - 1996 Focus Session - "Connecting with Communities", July 1996; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3976, Folder 1)
  - 1996 RA "Focus Teaser #2", July 1, 1996; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 6)
  - 1997 NEA Friend of Education RA Address - Atlanta, Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3975, Folder 1)
  - 1997 NEA RA Highlights- Atlanta, Series 1 (Box 4633, Folder 1)
  - 1997 NEA RA International Guests and Speaker, Series 1 (Box 4633, Folder 2)
  - 2003 NEA Human and Civil Rights Awards Dinner New Orleans, July 2, 2003; Series 1 (Box 4633, Folder 3)
  - ACT 11/27/70: Tape 1 D. Wilson, C. Blaschke, K. Bowden, D. Davies, J. Hobson, H. Scott, November 27, 1970; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3947, Folder 1)
  - ACT 11/27/70: Tape 2 Reactions; Questions & Answers, November 27, 1970; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3948, Folder 1)
  - ACT 11/28/70: Tape 1 Group Reports, November 28, 1970; Series 1; audio reel-to-reel (Box 3949, Folder 1)
  - ACT (?) Meeting, July 28, Undated; Series 1; audio reel-to-reel (Box 3950, Folder 1)
  - ACT Tape on Copyright Bill S-543, Undated; Series 1; audio reel-to-reel (Box 3951, Folder 1)
  - Adlai Stevenson, 1955; Series 1; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 1)
  - Al Gore - Acceptance Speech - Democratic National Convention - CNN, 1992; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3960, Folder 1)
  - Al Gore Introduction for Representative Assembly, 1995; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3952, Folder 6)
  - "Art" – Mayo Bryce, Dean School of Fine & App. Arts, No Ill. U. Tuesday, March 27, 1:30 pm, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3884, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Morgan Tribute (RA Presentation Version), June 24, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 1)
  - Bill Clinton AFL-CIO Convention, 1993; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3960, Folder 4)
  - Bill Clinton AFL-CIO Convention, 1995; Series 1 (Box 3960, Folder 5)
  - Bill Clinton's Satellite Downlink to Auditorium, May, 1992; Series 1 (Box 3960, Folder 6)
  - "Biological Science" – Hulda Grobman, consultant Biological Sciences Curriculum Study, American Institute of Biological Sciences, U. of Clo.Tuesday, March 27, 1:30 pm, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3884, Folder 2)
  - Bob Chase Keynote, 1997; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 2)
  - Bob Chase Keynote Address - NEA RA 2000, July 13, 2000; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3976, Folder 2)
  - Bob Chase Remarks to 11th Annual Technology & learning Conference, October 31, 1997; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3975, Folder 2)
  - Bob Chase Video Message to Ohio Educ. Assoc. (RA), November 2, 2001; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 3)
  - Bob Chase Welcome for RA 2001 Website, Februar 5, 2001; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 4)
  - Bob Dole Speech to U.S. Conference of Mayors - Miami, Florida, June 17, 1995; Series 8 (Box 3960, Folder 8)
  - Bylaw 3-1-G 1999 NEA RA, June 25, 1999; Series 1 (Box 4633, Folder 4)
  - Class of '97 Presentation Atlanta, May 30, 1997; Series 1 (Box 4633, Folder 5)
  - Class of '98 Presentation New Orleans, June 12, 1998; Series 1 (Box 4633, Folder 6)
  - Classroom Teachers Conference: "Education for the Exponential Age" - Clarence A. Weber, July 7, 1965; Series 1; 1/4" single track magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3771, Folder 13)
  - Classroom Teachers Conference: "Heritage and Horizons" - Libby Kontz, July 16, 1965; Series 1; 1/4" single track mangetic audio tape, 7 1/2 IPS. (Box 3816, Folder 1)
  - Classroom Teachers Conference "New England's Historical Heritage" Albert E. Van Dusen, November 26, 1971; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS single track audio reel-to-reel (Box 3908, Folder 3)
  - Commitment to Action #1, 1968; Series 1; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 2)
  - Commitment to Action #2, 1968; Series 1; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 3)
  - Conference on the Dropout: Tape 1 Morning and Start of Afternoon: Hoyt, Moor, Varner, Keppel, Bowman, October, 1963; Series 1; reel-to-reel audio (Box 3897, Folder 2)
  - Conference on the Dropout: Tape 2 Afternoon Session: Bowman, Putnam, Brooks, Petrich, October, 1963; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3897, Folder 3)
  - Conference on the Dropout: Tape 3 Afternoon Session and Evening: Petrich, Williams, McGraw, Couse, October, 1963; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3897, Folder 4)
  - Conference on the Dropout: Tape 4 Evening Session and Morning Session: Couse, Putnam, Ulrich, October, 1963; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3897, Folder 5)
  - Conference on the Dropout: Tape 5 Morning Session and Afternoon Session: Ulrich, Putnam, Zalero, Bowman; Recommendation, October, 1963; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3897, Folder 6)
  - Conference on the Dropout: Tape 6 Afternoon Program: Recommendation, October, 1963; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3897, Folder 7)
  - Conference Series: Keith Geiger, Governor King, Education Secretary Robert Riely and Vice President Al Gore addresses Audience, April 8, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3962, Folder 10)
  - Conference Series: Vice President Al Gore and Education Secretary Robert Riely visits High Tech Classroom - Online & Speeches - All B-Roll, April 8, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3962, Folder 9)
  - Conference Series: Vice President Al Gore's Speech - departure down the hall and the reception in the exhibit area - roll 3, April 8, 1994; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3963, Folder 1)
  - Contract with America From: Dave Kopeck, Undated; Series 1; BEATCAM video tape (Box 3963, Folder 2)
  - "Creativity" – Calvin Taylor, Prof. of Psych., Univ. of Utah Wednesday, March 28, 10:30 am, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3893, Folder 1)
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Charles Bish - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 25, 1963; Series 1; 2.35 (Box 3543, Folder 8)
    Bish, Charles E. (Charles Edward)
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Daniel Schreiber - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 26, 1963; Series 1; 1.85 (Box 3543, Folder 9)
    Schreiber, Daniel
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Dr. James E. Russell - 25 min. - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 25, 1963; Series 1; 12-15 2.30 (Box 3543, Folder 10)
    Russell, James E.
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Elizabeth Sutton - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 26, 1963; Series 1; 150 (Box 3543, Folder 11)
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - George Arnstein - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 25, 1963; Series 1; 1.85 (Box 3554, Folder 1)
    Arrangement
    Offsite in a shared box with box 3653, 3649, 3654, 3655, 3648, 3651, 3645, 3644, 3635
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Glenn Snow - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 27, 1963; Series 1; 1.85 (Box 3543, Folder 12)
    Snow, Glenn E.
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Hazel Blachard - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 26, 1963; Series 1; 1.85 (Box 3556, Folder 1)
    Blanchard, Hazel Ann
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Paul Smith - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 26, 1963; Series 1; 150 (Box 3557, Folder 1)
    Smith, Paul E.
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Thelma Pugh - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 26, 1963; Series 1; 150 (Box 3558, Folder 1)
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Walter Waetjen - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 25, 1963; Series 1; 2.35/24 (Box 3558, Folder 2)
  - Dallas Regional 1963 - Waurine Walker - NEA Regional Meeting - Dallas, Texas, March 27, 1963; Series 1; 1.85/10 (Box 3558, Folder 3)
    Walker, Waurine
  - Day of the Doers: President Johnson at NEA Convention, 1965; series 1 (Box 4588, Folder 3)
  - Day of the Doers: President Johnson at NEA Convention, 1965; series 1; 16mm Film (Box 4541, Folder 4)
  - Democratic National Committee "These Are the Days" Grunwald Eskew & Donilon, June 23, 1994; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3963, Folder 5)
  - Democratic National Committee - "Partnership" - Gore / Clinton, June 29, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3963, Folder 6)
  - Democratic National Convention - NEA President Keith Geiger, July 15, 1992; Series 1; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4028, Folder 7)
  - Department of Classroom Teachers Study Conference on Performance-Based Teaching: Tape 1 Washington, DC, November 26, 1971; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3908, Folder 1)
  - Department of Classroom Teachers Study Conference on Performance-Based Teaching: Tape 2 Washington, DC, November 26, 1971; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3908, Folder 2)
  - Discussion "National Defence Education Act and School Legislation" Wednesday, March 28, 10:30 am, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3884, Folder 9)
  - Don Cameron - Address 1997 NEA RA - Atlanta, Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3975, Folder 3)
  - Don Cameron - NEA RA 2000, July 13, 2000; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3976, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Taye Woldesmaite Pres.- Ethiopia Teachers Association NEA RA- New Orleans, July 4, 2003; Series 1 (Box 4633, Folder 7)
  - Dropout, February 1, 1962; Series 1; reel-to-reel audio (Box 3897, Folder 1)
  - Dropout Conference Tape #1, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS half track audio reel-to-reel (Box 3897, Folder 9)
  - Dropout Conference Tape #2, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS half track audio reel-to-reel (Box 3897, Folder 10)
  - Dropout Conference Tape #3, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS half track audio reel-to-reel (Box 3897, Folder 11)
  - Doris E. Lee - Spokane Regional Conference 1966 - The Culturally Deprived - # 6 Master Tape broken at end of speech, Undated; Series 1; 3 3/4 IPS Full Track (Box 3558, Folder 4)
  - Dr. Anna Hyers WCOTP, Address: Paris France 1964, Series 1; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 4)
  - Education International 1998 World Congress Highlights, July 29, 1999; Series 1 (Box 4633, Folder 8)
  - Education International 1998 World Congress Opening Ceremony Performance, Series 1 (Box 4633, Folder 9)
  - Education International 1998 World Congress Washington, DC "Bill Clinton", August 17, 1998; Series 1 (Box 4634, Folder 1)
  - Education International 3rd World Congress- 2001 Opening Video, June 25, 2001; Series 1 (Box 4634, Folder 2)
  - Education International Address by: Thulas Nxesi, RA 2000, August 1, 2000; Series 1 (Box 4634, Folder 3)
  - Education International "Kosovo Tribute", undated; Series 1 (Box 4634, Folder 4)
  - Education International World Congress, June 26, 1995; Series 1 (Box 4634, Folder 5)
  - Educational International World Congress "Amendments to the Constititution", July 27, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 5)
  - Educational International World Congress "Amendments to the Constititution, Membership Dues", July 27, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 6)
  - Educational International World Congress "Awards Dinner" 1, July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 7)
  - Educational International World Congress "Awards Dinner" 2, July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 8)
  - Educational International World Congress "Business Session" 1, July 26, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 9)
  - Educational International World Congress "Business Session" 2, July 26, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 10)
  - Educational International World Congress "Business Session" 3, July 26, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 11)
  - Educational International World Congress "Business Session" 4, July 26, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 12)
  - Educational International World Congress "Business Session" 5, July 26, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 13)
  - Educational International World Congress "Elections & Awards", July 25, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 14)
  - Educational International World Congress "Elections to the Executive Board, Resolutions", July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 15)
  - Educational International World Congress "Financial Reports, Elections - Executive Board, Programs & Budget" 1, July 27, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 16)
  - Educational International World Congress "Financial Reports, Elections - Executive Board, Programs & Budget", July 27, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 17)
  - Educational International World Congress "Opening Session", July 25, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 18)
  - Educational International World Congress "Opening Session" 2, July 25, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 19)
  - Educational International World Congress "Presentations, Amendment to the Consitutition", July 27, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4025, Folder 20)
  - Educational International World Congress "Resolutions" 1, July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3994, Folder 18)
  - Educational International World Congress "Resolutions" 2, July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3994, Folder 19)
  - Educational International World Congress "Resolutions" 3, July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3994, Folder 20)
  - Educational International World Congress "Resolutions" 4, July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3994, Folder 21)
  - Educational International World Congress "Resolutions" 5, July 289, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3994, Folder 22)
  - Educational International World Congress, "Resolutions" [1/3], July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM SP Video Cassette (Box 4707, Folder 1)
  - Educational International World Congress, "Resolutions" [2/3], July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM SP Video Cassette (Box 4707, Folder 2)
  - Educational International World Congress, "Resolutions" [3/3], July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM SP Video Cassette (Box 4707, Folder 3)
  - Educational International World Congress, "Resolutions, Bill Clinton, Unfinished Business, Presentation Child Labor" [1/3], July 29, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM SP Video Cassette (Box 4707, Folder 4)
  - Educational International World Congress, "Resolutions, Bill Clinton, Unfinished Business, Presentation Child Labor" [2/3], July 29, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM SP Video Cassette (Box 4707, Folder 5)
  - Educational International World Congress, "Resolutions, Bill Clinton, Unfinished Business, Presentation Child Labor" [3/3], July 29, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM SP Video Cassette (Box 4707, Folder 6)
  - Educational International World Congress "Resolutions, Bill Clinton, Unfinished Business, Presentation Child Labour" 1, July 29, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3994, Folder 23)
  - Educational International World Congress "Resolutions, Bill Clinton, Unfinished Business, Presentation Child Labor" 2, July 29, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3994, Folder 24)
  - Educational International World Congress "Resolutions, Bill Clinton, Unfinished Business, Presentation Child Labor" 3, July 29, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3994, Folder 25)
  - EI World Congress '98 Tape #1, July 25, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4023, Folder 7)
  - EI World Congress '98 Tape #2, July 25, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4023, Folder 8)
  - EI World Congress '98 Tape #3, July 25, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4023, Folder 9)
  - EI World Congress '98 Tape #5, July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4023, Folder 10)
  - EI '98 World Congress Tape #6A, July 28, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4024, Folder 1)
  - EI '98 World Congress Tape #9, July 29, 1998; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 4024, Folder 2)
  - "Electronic and Learning Labs" – Sister Mary Theresa Brentano O.S.B., Mount St. Scholastica Tape Institute, Atchinson, Kansas Wed, March 28, 10:30 am, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS reel-to-reel audio (Box 3893, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth Duncan Koontz - Audio Recording, Undated; Series 1; Koontz, Elizabeth D. (Elizabeth Duncan); 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3717, Folder 8)
  - "English" – G. Robert Carlsen, Prof. of Educ., State U. of Iowa March 27, 1:30 pm, Undated; Series 1; 3 ¾ IPS audio reel-to-reel (Box 3884, Folder 3)
  - ERA - The Equal Rights Amendment and You: Congressperson Margaret Heckler, 1975; Series 1; Audio cassette. (Box 3703, Folder 2)
    Speech from 1975 NEA Annual Meeting.
  - Excerpts from Clinton's Speech tp the Democratic National Convention, September 1996; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 5)
  - Government Relations NEA-PAC, April 26, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3965, Folder 4)
  - Governor Bill Clinton speaks to NEA-PAC, 1991; Series 1 (Box 3965, Folder 3)
  - Great Falls, Mont. Northwest Regional Conference, 1961: Dr. Lee, Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3721, Folder 1)
  - Great Falls, Mont. Northwest Regional Conference, 1961: Dr. Ramstad, Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3721, Folder 2)
  - Great Falls, Mont. Northwest Regional Conference, 1961: Dr. Richard Miller, Series 1; Miller, Richard; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3721, Folder 3)
  - Great Falls, Mont. Northwest Regional Conference, 1961: Dr. Russell, Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3721, Folder 4)
  - Great Falls, Mont. Northwest Regional Conference, 1961: Ewald Turner, Series 1; Turner, Ewald; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3721, Folder 5)
  - Great Falls, Mont. Northwest Regional Conference, 1961: Lois Clark, Series 1; Clark, Lois M.; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3721, Folder 6)
  - Great Falls, Mont. Northwest Regional Conference, 1961: Moore - Introduction - Dr. Stinnett, Series 1; 1/4" magentic audio tape, no indicated speed. (Box 3721, Folder 7)
  - Great Falls, Mont. Northwest Regional Conference, 1961: Mr Abbott, Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no indicated speed. (Box 3616, Folder 13)
  - Great Falls, Mont. Northwest Regional Conference, 1961: Russell, James A., Series 1; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no indicated speed. (Box 3721, Folder 8)
  - Greensboro, North Carolina NEA/NBCT Summit, August 2005; Series 1; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 1)
  - Harold E. Wigren - Spokane Regional Conference - 1966 - Use of TV in the In-Service Education of Teachers, Series 1; 3-3/4 IPS Full Track (Box 3558, Folder 5)
    Wigren, Harold E.
  - Harold E. Wigren - Spokane Regional Conference 1966 - Use of TV in the In-Service Education of Teachers, Series 1; 3-3/4 IPS Full Track (Box 3558, Folder 6)
  - Harold E. Wigren - Spokane Regional Conference - 1966 - Use of TV in the In-Service Education of Teachers - Master Side 1 and Side 2, Series 1; 3 3/4 IPS Full Track (Box 3558, Folder 7)
  - Herndon: March 19, 1976, Series 1; Herndon, Terry; Magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3688, Folder 1)
  - Highlights 1976, Series 1; Magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3698, Folder 5)
  - Highlights 1998 Representative Assembly, July 15, 1998; Series 1 (Box 4634, Folder 6)
  - Highlights of the 1965 White House Conference on Education, Series 1; Recorded Audio Tape 19 min., 15 sec. 3-3/4 i.p.s. (Box 3663, Folder 7)
    Separated Materials
    Separated materials found in Box 3661 File 11 Filmstrip
  - Highlights RA 2000, July 13, 2000; Series 1 (Box 4634, Folder 7)
  - Hillary Clinton Introduction to 1994 RA, June 29, 1994; Series 1; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 3)
  - Hillary Clinton - Video Introduction 1994 NEA Representative Assembly, Series 1 (Box 3965, Folder 9)
  - H.I.V. and Body Fluids, Undated; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 3966, Folder 1)
  - H.I.V. - Facts About Transmission, Undated; Series 2 (Box 3966, Folder 2)
  - H.I.V. - Facts About Transmission - old - has been revised, Undated; Series 2 (Box 3966, Folder 3)
  - How it Works, May 11, 2001; Series 1; BETACAM video tape (Box 3995, Folder 7)
  - International Guests and Speaker - 1997 NEA RA - Atlanta, Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3975, Folder 4)
  - International Program RA- Dallas, Texas, 2002; Series 1 (Box 4634, Folder 8)